aetraffic.com 2013-04-25

# privacy | Aetraffic

The privacy of our visitors and subscribers is important to AETraffic. This statement contains important information regarding the personal information that AETraffic collects and how AETraffic uses that information.

## Personal Information Gathering

When you subscribe to our newsletter, AETraffic may collect information about:

  * your use of this website
  * your contact details for the purpose of registering with the website
  * transactions carried out over this website

## Personal Information Use

AETraffic might use your information to:

  * administer our website/newsletter
  * personalize our website/newsletter for you
  * allow your access and use of our website and newsletter services
  * publish information about you in the newsletter or on our website
  * send you products/services that you register for or purchase
  * send you statements/invoices and to collect payments
  * send you promotional content

When you register for our newsletter, your personal information will not be:

  * traded for any reason, including to gain information from other companies/people
  * sold/rented for any reason, including for any financial transaction
  * used in any way which would break our adherence to the CAN-SPAM Act

AETraffic could be required to or opt to disclose your information to agents/sub-contractors for the above purposes, and those parties must also use it according to the terms of this privacy statement.

If necessary, your information may be disclosed, if required or compelled to do so by legal authorities, in regards to legal actions and court order, and to take a legal position against these actions or orders.

## Securing Your Personal Data

AETraffic will take practical technical and administrative actions to avoid the misuse, loss, or alteration of your personal information.

AETraffic will store your information on our secure servers to the best of our ability, and information entered into our website will be protected by encryption technology.

## Cross-Border Data Storage and Transfer

Information that AETraffic which is collected may be processed, transferred or stored in different servers or data centers owned by different corporate entities in all countries in which AETraffic operates in order to use the information in agreement with this privacy policy. By subscribing to our service, you agree to these cross-border transfers of your information.

Also, any personal information you submit for publication on our website or in our newsletter may be published on the internet.

## Third Party Websites

This website may contain links to other websites that may or not be affiliated with AETraffic, but we are not responsible for privacy policies/practices of any third party.

## About this Privacy Statement

This privacy statement may be updated at any time and should be checked by your frequently, to maintain familiarity with our policies.  If you do not agree to our privacy policy or are otherwise unsatisfied with our services, you are free to cancel your membership at any time.
